This is the Tianshu Medicine Array.
That's right.
He still needs to inject magic power into these formations.
This is the greatest protection
he can give your entire city.
Right,
Master?
Don't call me Master.
Brother Qingxuan.
I only know this Tianshu Medicine Array is a closely guarded secret.
I've only heard its name but don't know the details.
To see it today
is the honor of a lifetime.
Thank you, Master.
You can rest here first.
We'll go look for the materials right away.
I shall take my leave now.
Let me know if you need anything.
It is dangerous here,
and the matter in Ercheng
has nothing to do with you anyway.
You'd better leave as soon as possible.
I'm not leaving. I want to follow you, Master,
to slay demons.
Slay demons?
Do you think that with your broken bow,
you can defeat that kind of great demon?
She has lived for thousands of years.
I don't care if she's an old hag who's lived for hundreds
or thousands of years.
Old hag?
Master, please teach me.
I want to do my part too.
What about you?
Me?
I have nothing else to do anyway.
If I can protect the people of Ercheng with Brother Qingxuan,
it can be considered accumulating some good karma.
Whatever you want.
I'm going back to rest.
Have a good rest, ancestor.
Sister Gesang,
so he's willing to teach me, right?
I couldn't tell.
Little brother,
you were exceptionally brave today.
Have you never learned spells before?
I haven't. I've only practiced archery.
I usually hunt wild game
to provide food for the village.
Then you must follow my ancestor
and practice hard.
In time, you will surely achieve greatness.
Lord Hu really has a good eye.
I think so too.
You think so too?
That's great.
You need to practice hard.
Then I'll go back to my room to rest.
Don't come to me even if you need something.
Rest early, Lord Hu.
I beg for an answer.
What is the origin of the owner of this hair?
The reincarnation of an immortal.
The reincarnation of an immortal?
Banished to the mortal realm?
No.
What's his story with Qingxuan?
What's their specific connection?
I cannot say.
Then what was his name as an immortal?
Bai Jingqing.
That sounds
like a woman's name.
Master,
it's me, Hu San.
Master, I have something to report.
Can I come in and talk?
Come in.
Master,
today I saw you put a spell
on Feilu's bow and arrows.
But he has never practiced magic before.
The power of this arrow is extraordinary.
I actually think
that mortals
can also be destined
to be blessed by other spiritual powers,
borrowing external forces.
This world is vast,
with all kinds of phenomena.
Everything happens for a reason.
Feilu's bow can have such power.
It seems beyond common sense,
but if you investigate its origin,
it is also within the creation of heaven and earth.
My ancestors were indeed right.
This flying deer
is indeed extraordinary.
It came from the heavens.
You can observe the world.
Have you cultivated the Heavenly Eye?
No.
You couldn't have.
Those who cultivate the Heavenly Eye
can observe the return of spiritual energy,
see the changes in Yin, Yang, and the Five Elements,
perceive the true forms of immortals, gods, ghosts, and demons,
and see fate and reincarnation.
This is beyond ordinary people.
You are just a third-grade warlock.
You couldn't have.
Naturally, I can't do it.
But,
our Bureau of Astronomy has always had the right to observe the heavens,
and we possess ancient artifacts to seek divine answers.
So,
what did this divine artifact of yours
tell you exactly?
It said,
"Heaven's secrets must not be revealed."
So it didn't say anything else.
But ancestor.
Do you know
a High Immortal named Bai Jingqing?
Bai Jingqing.
High God.
Why are you here again?
You remember me, High God.
I wonder if the High God has found a way
to refuse severing the seven emotions
and still reach the Nine Heavens to become an immortal?
There are many cultivators in the world.
Those who have the fate to come here
are very few.
You have a deep affinity with immortality.
In just 500 years,
I have seen you twice.
But you gave up the path to immortality to keep your emotions.
Ridiculous.
What a pity.
I have an appointment with someone.
And now...
What about now?
Above the immortal steps,
do you think coming and going in my Sanshan School is child's play?
No, High God.
I just...
Your mind is unclear,
and your senses are not pure.
You'd better go back and cultivate for another thousand years.
Then can I stay here for a few days
to comprehend Taoism
and also
accompany you, High God?
This is a place for cultivating immortality.
How can I let a monster like you stay here?
Leave now.
Then I shall leave this lingering thought of longing.
A lingering thought of longing
can help me survive the cold.
What kind of obsession is it
that makes you waver about becoming an immortal?
If you speak of obsession,
there is only one.
Do you know
that a great disaster is coming to you?
A great disaster is coming?
Why do you say that, High God?
I truly do not understand.
You have traveled back and forth to Sanshanliu many times
and left just as many times.
Such behavior has long violated the Heavenly Dao.
If this time
you still refuse to sever your emotions
and insist on leaving,
then...
Then what?
You will lose all your cultivation
and revert to your original form.
And for all eternity,
you will never set foot on the path to immortality again.
Ping Jieqiang, Hai Hui.